I promise, Mom, if we get pets, we'll take
care of them.  I think many
parents have heard that phrase.   Please
be aware that it is false.  That's a big
lie invented by children.
Today, I decided to take care of the
children's second bedroom and do a couple of
errands for Poupa.  For those who didn't
follow, the children wanted
a bedroom for sleeping, which I've already
made, and a room for the kids and for
the rabbits.  [music] So, I went
back to my favorite store
to buy a couple of things.  We went
home and started by emptying
the second bedroom.  We put all the
rabbits in the cage and put them in a
quiet place.  Just enough time for cleaning.  We
removed their entire enclosure and cleaned everything
underneath.  After that, we set up the
office because school will inevitably
resume sooner or later.  Then
I added a small sofa that we had had for a
long time with a rug.  I
added a layer of pillows, a small
side table and their favorite thing.  If you
're still here, comment on room number
2 and feel free to give me
advice on how to improve this room.
We redid the rabbit enclosure, we
cleaned everything, the bedding, the food bowl,
all the hay was changed and
everyone is happy.  For organization,
I put all the hay in a large,
more practical bin, the small treats
in a small jar, and the food
in a large one.  We made sure to
get enough for Junior so that
everyone could eat.  I added a little bit
of decoration and I think it looks pretty
good now.  However, it's already 8:45 PM.  The
three of us are home
today, so we have to rush to
make dinner.  We're going for loco
and shrimp.  I took a shower in
3 minutes max and we settled down in front of the
TV.  In short, kisses.  Mr.